<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yifan Wang</title>
    <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yifan Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023 Yifan Wang 
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:05:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cacayaya.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Collapsing Mind: How Language Topology Shapes Our Imagination</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/blogs/brain-rot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:05:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/blogs/brain-rot/</guid>
      <description>LLMs Can Get “Brain Rot” Recently, we published a paper examining what happens when large language models consume too much highly popular but low quality content such as viral tweets and short social posts. The results were striking: reasoning ability fell by 23 percent, long-context memory decreased by 30 percent, and simulated personality tests showed spikes in narcissism and psychopathy. Even after retraining on clean, high-quality data, the model struggled to fully recover.&#xA;We call this phenomenon “LLM Brain Rot”, as it closely resembles what can happen to the human mind when it is continuously exposed to shallow, repetitive, and emotionally charged information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom, Intelligence and Agent</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/blogs/freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 22:31:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/blogs/freedom/</guid>
      <description>The Role of Human “Freedom” and “Individuality” in the Evolution of Intelligence From Escape from Freedom&#xA;From an evolutionary perspective, the history of humankind can be seen as a process of deepening individuation and freedom. Humanity’s departure from the pre-human stage marked the first step away from the compulsion of instinct, marking the beginning of our quest for freedom.&#xA;If instinct represents a special behavioral pattern determined by our neural structure, we can observe a clear trend across the animal kingdom: the lower an animal’s level of development, the more perfectly it adapts to nature, and the more rigidly its behavior is governed by instinct and reflex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiteEmo App Development</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/projects/biteemo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:54:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/projects/biteemo/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed something quite common around me: most people aren&amp;rsquo;t struggling with their weight because they don&amp;rsquo;t know what to eat or how to exercise. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s often emotional issues—stress from work, social pressures, or just feeling down—that trigger unhealthy eating behaviors. Managing these emotions, rather than merely counting calories or forcing workouts into an already busy schedule, can be the key to better health.&#xA;From my own experience, writing down my thoughts and feelings—doing what I call a &amp;ldquo;brain dump&amp;rdquo;—has always been incredibly therapeutic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:39:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education 2022-Present Ph.D in Computer Science, Purdue University 2018-2022 B.E. in Electronic Information Engineering, University of Science and Technology of China Work Experience 2024.5 - 2024.12 Texas Instruments Large Langugae Model Research Intern, work with Dr. Fanping Sui. Research Experience 2022.9 - present Purdue University Research assistant, advised by Prof. Ananth Grama. 2021.6 - 2022.6 Institute for Artificial Intelligence, Peking University Research intern, advised by Prof. Aming Li. 2020.5 - 2022.5 Laboratory of cognitive neuropsychology, University of Science and Technology of China Research assistant, advised by Prof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 1 of example doc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 1 of nested chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 2 of example doc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cacayaya.github.io/docs/example-doc/nested-chapter/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter 2 of nested chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
